tradesy.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Tradesy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Tradesy, Inc. or any of its affiliates or subsidiaries (“Tradesy,” the “Company,” or “we”) collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information (including personal information) collected from users (each, a "User" or "you") of our website located at www.tradesy.com ("Website"), mobile applications and other services provided by Tradesy, Inc. or any of its subsidiaries (collectively, “Services”). 

By using the Website or any Services, or otherwise providing us with information, you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information and other information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we are not able to collect, store, use, and disclose information about you as set out in this Privacy Policy, we may not be able to provide you with access to the Website or Services. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

Tradesy has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page www.tradesy.com/privacy/ for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

## Information We Collect

### Personal information

We may collect personal information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Website or use our mobile application, register on the Website or for Services, place an order, list an item for sale, and in connection with other activities, services, features, or resources we make available using our Services. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, and phone number. Users may, however, visit our Website anonymously. We will collect personal information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal information, but it may prevent them from engaging in certain Website related activities or other Services. 

Tradesy is located in the United States, and when you use our Website and our Services, we collect, use and store your information in the United States. Your personal information will be subject to laws of the United States, which may differ from your country of residence. For example, the law of the United States may require that your personal information be disclosed to government agencies under different circumstances than in your country of residence. 

### Non-personal information

We may collect non-personal information about Users whenever they interact with our Website or Services. Non-personal information may include, but is not limited to, the browser name, the type of computer or device, and the technical information about Users’ means of connection to our Website or Services, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers utilized, mobile network information, and other similar information. 

### Web browser cookies

Our Website may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. Users’ web browsers place cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, we note that some parts of the Website may not function properly. 

### Seller Performance Information

We may use personal information to measure performance of sellers. 

## How we use information collected

In general, the personal information we collect is used for the primary purposes for which it was collected, including: 

##### To deliver our Services to you

Tradesy may use User’s personal information to deliver the Services and any other goods, services, or information that you request from Tradesy or any other user of the Tradesy Website or Services. 

##### To prevent, detect, and mitigate illegal activities

Tradesy may use User’s personal information to prevent, detect, and mitigate fraudulent, counterfeit, or illegal activities. 

##### To provide or improve customer service

We may use personal information to help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. 

##### To personalize user experience

We may use personal information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use our Services and resources provided on our Website. 

##### To improve our Website

We may use personal information obtained from feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 

##### To process payments

We may use personal information obtained when placing an order to provide service to that order. We only share this personal information with third-party payment providers, including Stripe, PayPal or Affirm, to the extent necessary to provide the service. 

##### To run a promotion, contest, survey, or other Website feature

We may use personal information to send information that Users have agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. 

##### To send periodic emails

We may use personal information such as email addresses to send Users information and updates pertaining to their order. A User's email address may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If a User agrees to be on our mailing lists, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

##### Unsubscribe/Opt-out

If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future promotion, content, survey, feature, or other marketing information or emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. You may not, however, unsubscribe from emails about your account status or order status.

##### Other uses

We may also use your personal information for a secondary purpose that is related to a purpose for which we collected it, where you would reasonably expect us to use your personal information for that secondary purpose. 

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices, and security measures that are designed to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information, and data stored on our Website or Services. 

### Disclosing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal information to others. 

Tradesy may disclose Users' personal information to the following parties and for the purposes for which it was collected as described above: 

##### Sellers from whom you have purchased items

When you buy an item on Tradesy, if the seller does not elect to use her own shipping materials, the seller receives a Tradesy-branded shipping kit with a pre-paid, pre-addressed postage label with your full street address. The information will only include that which is necessary and relevant to successfully complete your order. The seller is strictly prohibited from using your information for anything other than completing the sale. 

##### Business partners, trusted affiliates, and third party service providers

We may disclose generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers, without notification to the User of such disclosure. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and our Website or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending newsletters or surveys. We may disclose your information, including your personal information, to these third parties only to the extent necessary for them to provide such services to us and such third party service providers are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that information. These third parties may be located outside of your country of residence, including in Canada, Australia, or European Union (“Offshore Recipients”). In this case, your personal information would be subject to the laws of the country in which the Offshore Recipient is located, which may have laws that require that your personal information be disclosed to government agencies under different circumstances than would your country of residence. While Tradesy remains committed to protecting your personal information, you consent to this disclosure and acknowledge that Tradesy has no control over, and is not liable for, the acts and omissions of Offshore Recipients. 

We may use personal information obtained when placing an order to provide service to that order. We only share this personal information with third-party payment providers, including Stripe, PayPal or Affirm, to the extent necessary to provide the service. 

#####  Corporate Transactions 

In the event of a sale, amalgamation, re-organization, transfer or financing of parts of some or all of Tradesy’s business ("Transaction"), your personal information may be disclosed to an acquiring organization either as part of due diligence or on completion of the transaction. If your personal information is ever disclosed in this context, Tradesy will require the acquiring organization to agree to protect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and to only use your personal information for purposes relating to the Transaction. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

##### Law enforcement and government agencies

We may disclose User’s personal information as required by law, including to law enforcement and government agencies in response to a verified request related to suspected illegal activities or related to a criminal investigation. We will only disclose information that we find necessary and relevant ("Disclosed Information"). Disclosed Information may include a User’s name, mailing address, phone number, and email address. Disclosure may be made without notice to User. 

##### Third Parties with intellectual property rights

We may disclose User’s personal information to third parties with intellectual property rights who have complied with Tradesy’s complaint procedure, as outlined in our Terms of Use Agreement located at www.tradesy.com/terms/. We will only disclose information found necessary and relevant in connection to an intellectual property infringement, fraud investigation, or other unlawful activity to which the third party has been subject, as detailed in our Verified Rights Owners Program (Section 12 in our Terms of Use Agreement located at www.tradesy.com/terms/). Disclosed personal information may include, but is not limited to, User’s name, mailing address, phone number, and email address. Disclosure may be made without notice to User. 

For avoidance of doubt, please take note that disclosing personal information to third parties with intellectual property rights includes the disclosure of personal information of a User who has been identified as selling unauthorized goods or replica items, which is in violation of our Terms of Use Agreement. 

##### Third parties in a legal proceeding

We may disclose User’s personal information to third parties involved in a legal proceeding if the third party provides Tradesy with a subpoena or other similar lawful process. Disclosure may be made without notice to User. 

Tradesy will also disclose to third parties involved in a legal proceeding when Tradesy believes in good faith that disclosing personal information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or to report suspected illegal activity. 

##### Tradesy Users

We may use user information obtained from account activity including total number of sales, last active timeframe, and message response time, in order to provide seller performance information to Tradesy users. 

### Disclosure related to Tradesy’s Terms of Use Agreement

If Tradesy believes in good faith that a User has breached the Terms of Use Agreement or any other Tradesy agreement, Tradesy may disclose such User’s personal information as found necessary and relevant to pursuing a claim or preventing further injury to Tradesy, its Users, and others. Disclosure may be made without notice to User. 

## Third Party Websites and Advertising

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Website that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors, and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Website. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interacting on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Website, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. Tradesy is not a party to those agreements; they are solely between you and the third party. 

### Advertising

Advertisements appearing on our Website may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the advertising server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows advertising networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser. 

### Google Adsense

Some of the advertisements may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve advertisements to Users based on their visit to our Website and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non-personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google advertising and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. 

## Administration and How to Contact Us

### Storing Your Information

Tradesy will retain and store your personal information for as long as is necessary to provide you the Services and any other ancillary purposes. Following termination or deactivation of your account, Tradesy or its service providers may retain information (including your profile information) for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, and/or audit purposes. If you have any questions about termination or deactivation of your account, please contact us directly using the contact details below. 

### Opt out

If you would like to opt-out of communications from Tradesy, please follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of emails you receive from us or contact us directly using the contact details below.

### Access, correction and complaints

If you wish to access, correct, or update the personal information we hold about you, please contact us directly using the contact details below. Tradesy may charge a reasonable amount for providing access to personal information, or refuse access to personal information where permitted by law. 

If you have any questions or concerns about Tradesy’s collection, storage, use or disclosure of personal information, or if you believe that Tradesy has not complied with this Privacy Policy or applicable privacy law, please contact Tradesy using the contact details below. When contacting Tradesy, please provide as much detail as possible in relation to the question, issue or complaint. Your complaint will be taken seriously and will be assessed by an appropriate person with the aim of resolving any issue in a timely and efficient manner. Tradesy requests that you cooperate with Tradesy during this process and provide any relevant information that may be required. 

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Website or our Services, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use Agreement. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Website or Services. Your continued use of the Website and Services following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

### Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, our third party service providers or your dealings with any of our Services, please email [team@tradesy.com](mailto:team@tradesy.com) or contact us at: 

Tradesy Inc  
1217 2nd Street  
Floor 3  
Santa Monica, CA 90401  
844.988.7233 

##### For Canadian residents only:

For more information on your privacy rights, you may also contact the Canadian Federal Privacy Commissioner at: 

Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada  
112 Kent Street  
Place de Ville  
Tower B, 3rd Floor  
Ottawa, Ontario  
K1A 1H3 

##### For Australian residents only:

For more information on your privacy rights, you may also contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner at: 

Email: [enquiries@oaic.gov.au](mailto:enquiries@oaic.gov.au)  
Phone: +61-2-9284-9749  
Fax: +61-2-9284-9666  
Post: GPO Box 5218  
Sydney, NSW 2001  

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Tradesy who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of their personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [team@tradesy.com](mailto:team@tradesy.com). We may (and we may allow third-party service providers) use cookies or similar technologies to collect information about your browsing activities across different websites after you have used our Services. Our Services do not respond to "Do Not Track" (DNT) signals and operates as described in this Privacy Policy whether or not a DNT signal is received. 

Updated: April 2, 2018
